https://www.cartegraph.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Last Modified: 09/09/2020
At Cartegraph Systems, LLC (Cartegraph), we take your right to privacy seriously. That’s why we created this Privacy Policy—to detail the limited conditions in which your personal information is used. There may be certain areas on this site where you are requested to register or provide personal information in exchange for services, information or promotions. While your right to refuse to provide this information will not interfere with your ownership of Cartegraph’s products, it may prevent you from participating in certain programs or receiving information about new products and promotions. Your personal information, including your email address, is not sold or shared with anyone outside of Cartegraph or our authorized partners.
Use of Personal Information
Cartegraph may store and process personal information in order to better understand our customers’ needs, and therefore provide improved products and services. We may use your personal information to contact you about new products or promotional campaigns.
Cartegraph may also occasionally collect financial information (like credit card number and expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to quickly and accurately fulfill customer orders.
In some instances, Cartegraph may share information about customers and customer prospects with our authorized partners. Our partners are required to honor Cartegraph’s privacy guidelines and maintain the confidentiality of your personal information.
Security
Cartegraph is committed to keeping your personal data safe and we take every reasonable precaution to ensure security. Access to your personal information is restricted to the employees at Cartegraph and our authorized partners who have a specific need to view the data. Our employees and the employees of our partners are required to maintain the confidentiality of this information, and may not use this data for any purpose other than to complete the services required of their employment. Your personal data, including your email address, is used for internal purposes only and is never sold or shared with anyone outside of Cartegraph or our authorized partners unless we disclose information in response to a law enforcement request.
Links to Other Sites
Our website may contain links to other public and private websites. These links are provided for your convenience, however, Cartegraph assumes no responsibility for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Cartegraph encourages you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy practices may differ from ours.
Notification of Changes
Cartegraph may occasionally update, amend, or change this Privacy Policy as needed or appropriate. We reserve the right to modify this policy at our discretion. All policy changes will be posted in this area and we will revise the “Last Modified” date at the top of the policy.
Contacting Us About Your Information
If you would like to have your personal information deleted from our database, please email us at info@cartegraph.com or call 1.563.293.7757. You may also request to be removed from our mailing list when you receive our email newsletters by following the steps detailed at the end of the message. Please keep in mind that if you have requested to have your information updated or deleted, there may be a 2-4 week period during which you may receive information while we are completing that update/deletion.
Use of Data
In order to better understand how our customers are using the software, Cartegraph may access any data stored in the system— record count, usage frequency, type of assets being tracked, etc. This information is for internal use only and will help our team continue to develop an overall experience that will best fit your needs.
Third-Party License Attribution
The Cartegraph application contains third-party software licensed under the terms of separate open source software licenses, that Cartegraph is responsible for:
Cartegraph
.NET Framework (v4.8.2+): http://Microsoft.com
Accounting.js: http://openexchangerates.github.io/accounting.js/
Am Charts: https://anglesharp.github.io/
Anglesharp: http://www.amcharts.com/
Angular: https://github.com/angular/angular
Angular Material: https://material.angularjs.org/latest/
angular-bootstrap: https://github.com/angular-ui/bootstrap-bower
ComponentSpace: https://www.componentspace.com/saml-for-asp-net
core-js: https://github.com/zloirock/core-js#readme
Crystal runtime: https://www.sap.com/
CSLA: http://www.cslanet.com/
Date Format: http://blog.stevenlevithan.com/archives/date-time-format
DocumentFormat.OpenXML: https://www.nuget.org/packages/DocumentFormat.OpenXml/
Dotspatial Projections: https://github.com/DotSpatial/DotSpatial
Dragular: http://luckylooke.github.io/dragular/
Dynatree: https://code.google.com/p/dynatree/
ELMAH: https://code.google.com/p/elmah/
EntityFramework: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/ef/
Error-stack-parser.js: https://github.com/stacktracejs/error-stack-parser
Google APIs Auth MVC Extensions: https://www.nuget.org/packages/Google.Apis.Auth.MVC/
Google.Apis.Gmail v1 Client Library: https://www.nuget.org/packages/Google.Apis.Gmail.v1/
Handlebars: https://github.com/components/handlebars.js
HistoryJS: https://github.com/browserstate/history.js
HTMLSanitizer:https://github.com/mganss/HtmlSanitizer
IIS SDK for .NET: https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/dotnet/api/microsoft.web.administration?view=iis-dotnet
Insomnia-PhoneGap-Plugin:  https://github.com/EddyVerbruggen/Insomnia-PhoneGap-Plugin
Javascrpt.SourceMapper.NET: https://github.com/awestroke/Javascript.SourceMapper.NET
jqGrid: http://www.trirand.com/blog/
jQuery autoNumeric: http://www.decorplanit.com/plugin/
jQuery BlockUI Plugin: http://malsup.com/jquery/block/
jQuery Cookie Plugin: https://github.com/carhartl/jquery-cookie
jQuery Hashchange Plugin: http://benalman.com/projects/jquery-hashchange-plugin/
jQuery Migrate: https://github.com/jquery/jquery-migrate
jQuery MouseWheel: https://github.com/jquery/jquery-mousewheel
jQuery Splitter: http://krikus.com/js/splitter
jQuery Templating Plugin: https://github.com/BorisMoore/jquery-tmpl
jQuery Timepicker Addon: http://trentrichardson.com/examples/timepicker/
jQuery UI Touch Punch: http://touchpunch.furf.com/
jQuery UI: http://jqueryui.com/
jQuery Unobtrusive Validation: https://github.com/aspnet/jquery-validation-unobtrusive
jQuery Validation Plugin: http://bassistance.de/jquery-plugins/jquery-plugin-validation/
jQuery: http://jquery.com/
jquery.ui.dialog.patch.js: http://bugs.jqueryui.com/ticket/4671
jQuery: http://jquery.com/
json2typescript: https://github.com/dhlab-basel/json2typescript#readme
jsUri: https://github.com/derek-watson/jsUri
Jszip: https://github.com/Stuk/jszip#readme
justified-layout: https://github.com/flickr/justified-layout#readme
kendo-ui: https://www.telerik.com/kendo-ui
Knockout Mapping: http://knockoutjs.com/
knockout.merge: https://github.com/grofit/knockout.merge
Knockout: http://knockoutjs.com/
knockout-sortable: https://github.com/rniemeyer/knockout-sortable
knockout-validation: https://github.com/Knockout-Contrib/Knockout-Validation
Leaflet: https://leafletjs.com/
Less: https://github.com/less/less
Lodash: https://github.com/lodash/lodash
log4net: https://logging.apache.org/log4net/
LumenWorks.Framework.IO: http://www.codeproject.com/Articles/9258/A-Fast-CSV-Reader
Magick.NET: https://github.com/dlemstra/Magick.NET/blob/master/License.txt
material-design-icons: https://github.com/google/material-design-icons
MetadataExtractor: https://github.com/drewnoakes/metadata-extractor
Microsoft Application Insights: https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/application-insights/
Microsoft ASP.NET MVC: http://www.asp.net/mvc
Microsoft Visual C++ 2015 Redistributable (x64): https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/download/details.aspx?id=48145
Microsoft.ASPNET: https://www.microsoft.com/web/webpi/eula/aspnet_and_web_tools_2012_2_rtw_eula_enu.htm
AspNet.Web.Optimization: http://www.nuget.org/packages/Microsoft.AspNet.Web.Optimization/
Microsoft.NET: http://microsoft.com
Microsoft.NETCore: https://dotnet.microsoft.com/download/dotnet-core
Microsoft.SqlServer.Types: http://microsoft.com
Mime: https://github.com/broofa/mime#readme
mime-types: https://github.com/jshttp/mime-types#readme
Mixpanel: https://mixpanel.com/
mjolnic-bootstrap-colorpicker: https://github.com/mjolnic/bootstrap-colorpicker
NETStandard.Library: https://www.nuget.org/packages/NETStandard.Library/
Newtonsoft.json: https://www.newtonsoft.com/json
Newtonsoft.Json: https://www.nuget.org/packages/newtonsoft.json/
ng2-dragula: https://github.com/valor-software/ng2-dragula#readme
ng-file-upload-shim: https://github.com/danialfarid/angular-file-upload-bower
ngx-build-plus: https://github.com/manfredsteyer/ngx-build-plus#readme
Nlog: https://nlog-project.org
node-uuid: https://github.com/broofa/node-uuid
Oauth2: https://github.com/titarenko/OAuth2
object-fit-images: https://github.com/bfred-it/object-fit-images#readme
RazorGenerator.Mvc: https://github.com/RazorGenerator/RazorGenerator
RestSharp: http://restsharp.org/
Roboto Font (Google): https://fonts.google.com/specimen/Roboto
SQLite: https://system.data.sqlite.org/index.html/doc/trunk/www/index.wiki
ui-router/angular-hybrid: https://github.com/ui-router/angular-hybrid#readme
WebApiThrottle: https://github.com/stefanprodan/WebApiThrottle
WebGrease: http://webgrease.codeplex.com/
XmpCore: https://www.nuget.org/packages/XmpCore/
Cartegraph One
Amazon.Lambda.AspNetCoreServer: https://github.com/microsoft/tslib
cordova-plugin-camera: https://github.com/apache/cordova-plugin-camera
cordova-plugin-cartegraph-cookiemaster:https://www.npmjs.com/package/cordova-plugin-cookiemaster
cordova-plugin-cartegraph-datepicker: https://github.com/Cartegraph/cordova-plugin-datepicker
cordova-plugin-cookiemaster: https://www.npmjs.com/package/cordova-plugin-cookiemaster
cordova-plugin-customurlscheme: https://github.com/EddyVerbruggen/Custom-URL-scheme
cordova-plugin-datepicker: https://github.com/VitaliiBlagodir/cordova-plugin-datepicker
cordova-plugin-device: https://github.com/apache/cordova-plugin-device
cordova-plugin-file: https://github.com/apache/cordova-plugin-file
cordova-plugin-geolocation: https://github.com/apache/cordova-plugin-geolocation
cordova-plugin-ionic-keyboard https://github.com/ionic-team/cordova-plugin-ionic-keyboard
cordova-plugin-ionic-webview: https://github.com/ionic-team/cordova-plugin-ionic-webview
cordova-plugin-ios-no-export-compliance: https://github.com/mikaoelitiana/cordova-plugin-ios-no-export-compliance
cordova-plugin-network-information: https://cordova.apache.org/docs/en/latest/reference/cordova-plugin-network-information/
cordova-plugin-safariviewcontroller: https://www.npmjs.com/package/cordova-plugin-safariviewcontroller
cordova-plugin-splashscreen: https://github.com/apache/cordova-plugin-splashscreen
cordova-plugin-statusbar: https://github.com/apache/cordova-plugin-statusbar
cordova-plugin-whitelist: https://github.com/apache/cordova-plugin-whitelist
cordova-plugin-wkwebview-inject-cookie: https://github.com/CWBudde/cordova-plugin-wkwebview-inject-cookie#readme
cordova.plugins.diagnostic: https://github.com/dpa99c/cordova-diagnostic-plugin
cordova-plugin-safariviewcontroller: https://www.npmjs.com/package/cordova-plugin-safariviewcontroller
cordova-sqlite-ext: https://www.npmjs.com/package/cordova-sqlite-ext
ionic-plugin-keyboard: https://github.com/driftyco/ionic-plugin-keyboard
Ionicons: https://github.com/ionic-team/ionicons
lodash-es: https://lodash.com/
ionic-native: https://github.com/ionic-team/ionic-native
Microsoft Application Insights: https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/application-insights/
Mixpanel: https://mixpanel.com/
mixpanel-browser: https://github.com/mixpanel/mixpanel-js
Moment.js: http://momentjs.com/
ng-lazyload-image: https://github.com/tjoskar/ng-lazyload-image
Pendo: http://www.pendo.io
phonegap-plugin-barcodescanner: https://github.com/apache/cordova-plugin-file
Reactive Extensions for JavaScript RxJS): https://github.com/Reactive-Extensions/RxJS
reflect-metadata: https://github.com/rbuckton/ReflectDecorators
ModernHttpClient: https://components.xamarin.com/license/modernhttpclient
RestSharp: https://components.xamarin.com/view/restsharp
TinyIoC: https://github.com/grumpydev/TinyIoC
TinyMessenger: https://github.com/grumpydev/TinyMessenger
Xamarin Mobile: https://components.xamarin.com/view/xamarin.mobile
zxing.net.mobile: https://components.xamarin.com/view/zxing.net.mobile
